

Contact



Andijon viloyati Andijon tumani Intizor 122



+998 90970 70 78



aeraliyev@gmail.com



facebook.com/abbosbek.eraliyev

Skills

Elektromechanics

Working with circuits

Mechatronics

Innovative thinking

AutoCAD

FL studio

Adobe Photoshop

Hobbies









Eraliyev Abbosbek

Electromechanical engineer

About me

Due to my interest in electrical engineering and electronics from my youth, I graduated from the university in this direction and continue my research in this direction. In addition to my specialty, I am seriously involved in English, AutoCAD, mechatronics and programming.

Education

2012 - 2015

Andijan agroindustrial vocational college Accounting and auditing

2016 - 2020

Tashkent state technical university named after Islam Karimov, Power engineering faculty

Electrical engineering, electrical mechanics and electrical technologies (by branches)

Work experience

2014 -2015 | Ta'mirlovchi

Repair service for TV, DVD, radio and other types of players in the central market of Andijan region

2013 **-201**6

Computer maintenance

2017-2018 | Agregat Texplast

Presser